Register of the Victor Gilinsky Papers, 1943-1984
Hoover Institution Archives
- DOMESTIC NUCLEAR REACTOR LICENSING AND REGULATION, 1971-1984
  - Regulatory reform. NOTE: For about 18 months after the TMI accident, licensing approvals were suspended while the NRC conducted internal reviews of licensing procedures (in accordance with the TMI Action Plan). Materials related to these internal reviews are included in the following "General" c
    - Legislation
      - General
        - States' Participation, 1977 May-1978 July (Folder 5)
      - 1974 Sept.-1976 Oct. (Folder 6-7)
      - 1977. "Nuclear Regulatory Reform Act of 1977" (later known as "Nuclear Siting and Licensing Act of 1977")
        - April-July. Includes Udall hearing material, June 13, and comments from interested parties (Folder 8)
        - August-September
          - General. First Administration draft, Aug. 6; second Administration draft, Aug. 19 (Box 171., Folder 1-6)
          - Comments from interested parties (Folder 7-8)
          - Comments (contd.) (Box 172., Folder 1)
        - September-October
          - General. First NRC draft, Sept. 6; second NRC draft, Sept. 14; third NRC draft, Sept. 26 (Folder 2-6)
          - Comments from interested parties (Folder 7-8)
        - October (Folder 9)
        - October. Third Administration draft, Oct. 6; DOE draft, Oct. 14 (includes comments); NRC draft, Oct. 26 (Box 173., Folder 1-4)
        - November. DOE drafts, Nov. 2 and Nov. 14 (Folder 5-6)
        - December. DOE draft, Dec. 1 (Folder 7)
      - 1978. "Nuclear Siting and Licensing Act of 1978"
        - January. DOE draft, Jan. 4 (Folder 8)
        - February
          - General (Folder 9)
          - Hearings, Dingell Committee, Feb. 7-8 (Box 174., Folder 1-3)
        - March. Primarily an NRC report entitled "Improving Regulatory Effectiveness in Federal/State Licensing Actions," with extensive appendices consisting of comments from states (Folder 4-8)
        - April. Meeting transcript, April 3 (Folder 9)
        - May
          - General (Box 175., Folder 1-2)
          - Hearings
            - May 18, Hart/Simpson Committee hearing (Folder 3)
            - May 22 and 24-25, Udall Committee hearing (Folder 4-5)
        - June
          - General (Folder 6)
          - Hearings
            - June 6 (Folder 7)
            - June 12, 20, Udall Committee hearings (contd.) (Box 176., Folder 1-2)
            - June 28, Hart/Simpson Committee hearing (Folder 3)
        - July
          - General (Folder 4)
          - Hearings
            - July 12-13, Hart/Simpson Committee hearings (Folder 5-6)
            - July 18-19, Dingell Committee hearings (Folder 7-9)
            - July 20, Dingell Committee hearing (Box 177., Folder 1-3)
        - August-December (Folder 4-7)
      - 1979
        - Jan.-Feb. Includes NRC reports on issues which arose from 1978 hearings on regulatory reform legislation (Box 178., Folder 1-4)
        - March. Bevill Committee hearing, March 8; NRC draft March 14 (Folder 5-8)
        - April-Dec. NRC briefing, May 11 (Box 179., Folder 1-2)
      - 1980 March-Dec. Includes a memorandum on the Sholly v. NRC decision (Folder 3)
      - 1981
        - Jan.-Feb. Report on electric industry (Folder 4)
        - March
          - General (Folder 5)
          - Hearings, March 25 and 31, Hart/Simpson Committee hearings on the Sholly decision and licensing delays. Includes transcripts (Folder 6-8)
        - March. Includes NRC answers to follow-up questions posed by the committee (Box 180., Folder 1-2)
        - April-Oct. Includes estimates of costs of licensing delays, June-July (Folder 3-5)
      - 1982
        - Feb.-April. NRC briefing transcripts, Feb. 11 and April 16; NRC report on draft bills for proposed legislation, "Nuclear Standardization Act of 1982," March 25 (Folder 6-8)
        - April-June. Includes meeting transcripts, May 7, June 10 and 28, and draft text of bill and DOE recommendations on proposed legislation (Box 181., Folder 1-7)
        - June-Aug. Includes public comments on the proposed bill; meeting transcript, July 12 (Box 182., Folder 1-6)
        - August. Meeting transcripts, Aug. 4 and 31; NRC ad hoc committee report, Aug. 16 (Box 183., Folder 1-3)
        - Sept.-Nov. Task Force Report draft, Nov. 3 (Folder 4-7)
        - Dec. Ad hoc committee review of task force report, Dec. 1; cover memorandum with attached revision of legislation (now entitled "Nuclear Licensing Reform Act of 1983"), Dec. 7; meeting transcript, Dec. 16 (Box 184., Folder 1-6)
      - 1983
        - Jan. Meeting transcripts, Jan. 26-28 (Folder 7-11)
        - Feb.-April. NRC draft of legislation, "Nuclear Powerplant Licensing Reform Act of 1983," Feb. 4; proposed final NRC draft legislation, Feb. 15; meeting transcripts, March 15 and 24; NRC report on backfitting costs, April 4 (Box 185., Folder 1-9)
        - May-June. Meeting transcript, May 5; Hart/Simpson Committee hearing, May 25; Udall Committee hearing, June 9; NRC report on backfitting costs, June 22 (Box 186., Folder 1-9)
        - July-Dec. Meeting report, July 6; Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, Sept. 13, 21 and 23 (Box 187., Folder 1-9)
      - 1984 Jan.-April
- INTERNATIONAL REGULATION AND EXPORT LICENSING, 1946-1984
  - General
    - General. Primarily reports and speeches from a variety of sources relating to non-proliferation issues. SEE ALSO: SUBJECT FILE/Weapons
      - n.d. (Box 188., Folder 1)
      - 1956 Jan.-1975 May
      - 1976 Feb.-1978 Oct. Includes draft of a DOE report, "Nonproliferation Alternative Systems Assessment Program," 1977 May (Folder 2-9)
      - 1978 Nov.-1980 May. Includes DOE draft report, "United States Nuclear Education and Training Provided Foreigners--What are the Proliferation Implications?" 1978 Nov.; Council on Foreign Relations Discussion Group on Nuclear Non-proliferation, 1979 Dec. (Box 189., Folder 1-8)
      - 1980 June-Dec. DOE report, "Nuclear Proliferation and Civilian Nuclear Power" (Box 190., Folder 1-7)
      - 1980 July-1981 May (Box 191., Folder 1-7)
      - 1981 Nov.-1984 Jan. (Box 192., Folder 1-8)
    - Cooperative agreements. Notebook materials, largely specific cooperative agreements with individual countries
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Argentina-Spain (Box 193., Folder 1-7)
      - Sweden-Venezuela and Euratom (Box 194., Folder 1-3)
    - Export licensing
      - General
        - 1975 Feb.-1977 March. Includes an internal NRC report entitled, "Review of Export Licensing Procedures," 1976 Aug. (Folder 4-9)
        - 1977 May-1982 Feb. (Box 195., Folder 1-9)
        - 1982 April-1984 April (Box 196., Folder 1-6)
      - Export-Import Bank. Relates to health and safety issues for nuclear exports, 1975 Nov.-1978 June (Folder 7)
      - Export Licensing Study, 1975 Sept.-1977 Feb. (Box 197., Folder 1-2)
    - Import licensing, 1975 March-1976 June (Folder 3)
    - International Atomic Energy Agency (IAEA)
      - General. Sigvard Ecklund, Director General, 1975-1981. Speech transcripts and memoranda (Folder 4)
      - 1946. Report (Folder 5)
      - 1972-1973. Reports
      - 1975. Memoranda and meeting report
      - 1976. Reports and IAEA statute (Folder 6)
      - 1977. Conference materials and speech transcripts (Folder 7)
      - 1978. Report and letters
      - 1979. Report and letters (Box 198., Folder 1)
      - 1980-1981 Jan. Memorandum, pamphlet, reports and letters (Folder 2)
      - 1981 (Folder 3-4)
        - General. Primarily reports, May-Nov.
        - Hearings. Glenn/Percy Committee, Nov. 19; Senate Foreign Relations Committee, Dec. 2 (Folder 5-7)
          - General, 1981 Jan.-Dec.
          - Background materials, 1981 Nov.-Dec.
      - 1982
        - General. "International Safeguards System Effectiveness Evaluation" study performed for the NRC by Lawrence Livermore Lab, 1982 April-Oct. (Folder 8-9)
        - Jan.-Feb. Includes a copy of S. 1196, "International Security and Development Cooperation Act of 1981" (Box 199., Folder 1)
        - March
          - General (Folder 2)
          - Hearings. House Foreign Affairs Committee, Bingham/Bonker Subcommittee and Zablocki Subcommittee, March 3 and 18
        - April-July. IAEA Annual Report, May (Folder 7)
        - Sept. IAEA conference, Sept. (Folder 8)
        - Oct.-Dec. (Box 200., Folder 1)
      - 1983 Jan.-1984 Feb. (Folder 2-4)
    - Legislation, United States
      - General
        - General
          - 1975 Feb.-Dec. (Folder 5)
          - 1976 Feb.-1980 May (Folder 6-8)
          - 1981-1983 (Box 201., Folder 1)
        - Amendments, 1975 Oct.-1977 Jan. (Folder 2)
      - S. 1439, "Export Reorganization Act of 1976" and H.R. 15419, "Nuclear Explosive Proliferation Control Act of 1976"
        - General. Letters, bills, resolutions
          - 1975 April-1976 June. Glenn/Percy Committee hearings, 1976 Jan. l9, 20, 29 (Folder 3-6)
          - 1976 June-Sept. (Box 202., Folder 1-7)
          - 1976 Sept.-1977 Jan. (Box 203., Folder 1-2)
      - S. 897, "Nuclear Non-Proliferation Act of 1977/1978" and S. 1432, "Nuclear Non-Proliferation Policy Act of 1977/1978"
        - General. Letters, bills, notes, clippings, memoranda
          - 1977 Feb.-April (Folder 3-6)
          - 1977 April-1978 Feb. (Box 204., Folder 1-7)
          - 1978 Feb.-1979 Oct. (Box 205., Folder 1-4)
        - Hearings
          - 1977 May. Includes Glenn/Percy Committee, May 6 (Folder 5-7)
          - 1977 June. Senate Foreign Relations Committee, June 8 and 15; Church/Domenici Committee, June 10 (Box 206., Folder 1)
          - 1977 June-Sept. Church/Domenici Committee, Sept. 13-14 (Folder 2-4)
          - 1979. Udall Committee, July 26 (Folder 5)
      - H.R. 4409, 1977 March-1978 Feb. H.R. version of S. 897 (Folder 6-7)
      - H.R. 6032 and H.R. 6318. Legislation to strengthen the Nuclear Non-Proliferation Act of 1978. Primarily Zablocki and Bingham/Bonker Committee hearings, 1982 Aug. 10, Sept. 8-9 (Folder 8)
        - 1982 May-July
        - 1982 Aug.-Dec. (Box 207., Folder 1-2)
    - Plumbat incident. Relates to a book entitled, Operation Uranium Ship, about the disappearance (in 1968) of 200 tons of uranium while en route from West Germany to Italy, 1977 April-1979 March (Folder 3)
  - Canada. Speech transcripts relating to TMI, 1979 (Folder 4)
  - China, People's Republic of. Trip materials, 1983 May. Memorandum and State Department briefing book. (Folder 5)
  - Egypt. Materials relating to Dr. Gilinksy's trip, 1977 Sept.-Oct. Reports, statements, clipping, chart, memoranda, letters, miscellaneous administrative material, 1976-1977 (Folder 6)
  - France. Trip materials
    - 1978 ca. Sept.
      - Background material (Folder 7-8)
      - Correspondence (Folder 9)
    - 1983 April-May
      - Administrative material (Box 208., Folder 1)
      - Background material (Folder 2)
      - Correspondence (Folder 3)
  - Great Britain
    - General, 1977-1983 (Folder 4-5)
    - Windscale (reprocessing plant). Includes material relating to radiation releases and the fire of 1957
      - General
        - 1977-1984 (Folder 6-8)
      - "The Windscale Inquiry". Report by the Honorable Mr. Justice Parker for the Secretary of State for the Environment, 1978 Jan. (Folder 9)
  - India. Predominantly relating to the Tarapur nuclear plant
    - General
      - General
        - General
          - Clippings (collected by Dr. Gilinksy's office), 1973-1983 July (Box 209., Folder 1-6)
          - Notebook, 1956-1978 (Folder 7-8)
        - 1961-1980 Sept. (Box 210., Folder 1-7)
        - 1981 Feb.-1984 Feb. (Box 211., Folder 1-2)
      - Agreements for cooperation, 1956 March-1980 Feb. (Folder 3-4)
      - Bomb explosion, 1974 May-1978 April (Folder 5-6)
      - Energy plans, 1956-1975 (Box 212., Folder 1-2)
    - Exports
      - General (notebook), 1965 April-1980 March. Relates to the fueling schedule for the Tarapur reactor (Folder 3-6)
      - Licensing
        - General. Summary page. NOTE: The prefix "XSNM" refers to the export of special nuclear materials (SNM), primarily fuel, and "XSCOM" to reactor components (Box 213., Folder 1)
        - XSNM-726. 1975 Sept. 23 (Folder 2)
        - XSNM-805. 1976 March-Aug. (Folder 3-4)
        - XSNM-805/845
          - General
            - 1976 March-May (Folder 5-9)
            - 1976 May-Aug. (Box 214., Folder 1)
          - NRC hearings, 1976 March-Aug. (Folder 2-4)
          - Opinion, 1976 April 5-May 4 (Folder 5-7)
        - XSNM-845
          - General, 1975 Dec.-1977 July (Box 215., Folder 1-4)
          - NRC Hearings, 1976 July
            - General (Folder 5-6)
            - General (contd.) (Box 216., Folder 1-2)
            - Transcripts
              - July 20 (Folder 3-4)
              - July 21 (Folder 5-6)
          - Opinion, 1977 June 28 (Box 217., Folder 1)
        - XSNM-1060/1222
          - General
            - General. Notebook, 1978 July-1979 Jan. (Folder 2)
            - 1976 May-1978 June (Folder 3-7)
            - 1978 June-1979 March (Box 218., Folder 1-6)
          - Hearings, Congressional, 1978
            - May 23, House Committee on Foreign Affairs (Folder 7-8)
            - May 24, Senate Committee on Foreign Relations (Box 219., Folder 1)
            - June 6, House Committee on Foreign Affairs (Folder 2-3)
          - Opinions
            - XSNM-1060/1222, 1978 April 25
              - General (Folder 4)
              - Commissioners Gilinsky and Bradford (Folder 5-7)
              - Commissioners Gilinsky and Bradford (Contd.) (Box 220., Folder 1-2)
            - XSNM-1222, 1979 March 23
              - General (Folder 3)
              - Commissioners Gilinsky and Bradford (Folder 4)
        - Miscellaneous licensing actions (XSNM-1379, XSNM-1569, XSCOM-0240, XSCOM-0250, XSCOM-0376, XSCOM-0381, XSCOM-0395)
          - General
            - General. Notebooks
              - Fuel shipments (Folder 5)
              - Reactor components (Folder 6)
            - 1978 Oct.-1979 Oct. (Folder 7)
            - 1980 Jan.-1984 May (Box 221., Folder 1-6)
          - Hearing, Senate Committees on Foreign Relations (Frank Church, Chairman) and Governmental Affairs (Abraham Ribicoff, Chairman), 1980 June 18. Primarily background materials (Box 222., Folder 1-2)
          - Opinion (XSNM-1379), 1980 May 16
            - Final (Folder 3)
            - Drafts (Folder 4)
    - Heavy water, 1955 Oct.-1980 Dec. (Folder 5)
    - Legal research. Cases apparently related to intervenor status, 1970 March-1975 June (Folder 6-7)
  - Israel. Relates primarily to the Israeli raid on an Iraqi reactor, 1977-1981 June (Box 223., Folder 1-3)
  - Japan. Relates primarily to Dr. Gilinsky's trip (1977 March), including extensive background material
    - 1976 April-1977 March (Folder 4-9)
    - 1977 March-1981 Nov. The material from 1981 focuses primarily on the Tokai Mura reprocessing facility, including Bingham/Bonker Committee hearings, Oct. 29 and Nov. 4 (Box 224., Folder 1-4)
  - Korea. Safeguards analysis, 1982 (Folder 5)
  - Philippines. Relates to reactor export issues such as the quality assurance program, and a proposed location near areas of volcanic and seismic activity
    - 1979 Jan.-July (Folder 6-7)
    - 1979 Aug.-Oct. (Box 225., Folder 1-7)
    - 1979 Nov.-Dec. (Box 226., Folder 1-6)
    - 1980 Jan.-April (Box 227., Folder 1-6)
    - 1980 May-1981 May (Box 228., Folder 1-5)
  - South Africa. Relates to fuel exports
    - 1976 July-1977 April (Folder 6-8)
    - 1982 June-Dec. (Box 229., Folder 1)
  - Soviet Union. Primarily material on 1958 accident; also fuel sales, 1979 Aug.-1982 Oct. (Folder 2)
  - Spain
    - General, 1972 Jan.-1979 Nov. (Folder 3)
    - Export licensing, 1975 Oct.-1979 Nov. (Folder 4-5)
    - Reactors
      - General, 1976 May-1978 April (Folder 6)
      - ASCO II nuclear power plant
        - General, 1975 Sept.-1978 March (Folder 7)
        - Decision
          - Majority
            - Drafts 1-2 (Folder 8)
            - Drafts 3-11 (Box 230., Folder 1-5)
            - Final (Folder 6)
          - Commissioner Gilinsky. Drafts and notes (Folder 7)
          - Commissioner Gilinsky. Drafts and notes (contd.) (Box 231., Folder 1-8)
      - Valdecaballeros nuclear power plant, 1976 June-1977 May (Box 232., Folder 1-2)
  - Sweden. Summary of meeting with T. Westermark relating to underground siting, 1978 (Folder 3)
  - Taiwan, 1978 Jan.-1984 Feb. (Folder 4-9)
  - West Germany
    - 1976 July-1977 Feb. (Folder 10)
    - 1977 March-Dec. (Box 233., Folder 1-9)
- NUCLEAR REACTOR OPERATION, 1974-1984
  - General. NRC report and testimony transcript, 1982 (Box 234., Folder 1)
  - Backfitting. Policy development, 1979 Dec.-1984 July (Folder 2-7)
  - Decommissioning, 1978 Jan.-1984 June (Box 235., Folder 1-9)
  - Design and construction
    - General, 1976-1982. Includes EPRI report, "Human Factors Review of Nuclear Power Plant Control Room Design," 1976 Nov.; also includes materials relating to construction standards in Great Britain (Box 236., Folder 1-5)
    - Design standardization, 1979 Sept.-1983 Jan. (Folder 6)
    - Quality Assurance Program
      - 1978 Sept. Includes GAO report to Congress (Folder 7)
      - 1981 Oct.-1984 March. Includes Udall Committee hearing, 1981 Nov. 19; NRC report to Congress (draft), 1984 March (Box 237., Folder 1-6)
      - 1984 April-June. NRC report to Congress (final), April (Box 238., Folder 1-4)
  - Inspection and enforcement program. NOTE: This heading refers to routine inspection and assessment programs in addition to fines and enforcement procedures. Inclusion in this category may refer to allegations or investigations, but does not necessarily imply negligence or wrong-doing.
    - General. Primarily policy-making
      - Enforcement
        - 1980 March-April (Folder 5-9)
        - 1980 May-1984 Feb. (Box 239., Folder 1-6)
      - Investigation
        - General, 1982 Dec.-1984 March. Relates to the rights of those under investigation, complaints, and procedures during concurrent criminal investigations; also includes composite reports for specific plants (Folder 7)
        - Resident Inspector program, 1981 May-1983 March. Includes a NRC report to Congress, 1983 March (Folder 8)
        - Systematic Assessment of Licensee Performance (SALP) program. Includes reports on specific plants
          - 1979 Jan.-1980 Feb. (Folder 9)
          - 1980 Sept.-1981 Nov. (Box 240., Folder 1-4)
    - Automation Industries (alleged radiation exposure)
      - 1981 Feb.-1981 July (Folder 5-9)
      - 1981 Aug.-1983 June (Box 241., Folder 1-4)
    - Combustion Engineering (alleged falsification of test certificates), 1983 Aug. (Folder 5)
    - Eveleth Expansion Company (alleged employee over-exposure), 1982 Feb. (Folder 6)
    - George Washington University Medical Center (alleged inadequacy of radiation safety program), 1983 Sept. (Folder 7)
    - Hayward-Tyler (alleged problems with pumps)
      - 1982 Jan.-March. Includes investigation report (Folder 8-13)
      - 1982 March 23-April 7. Briefing materials and material relating to Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, April 6-7 (Box 242., Folder 1-9)
      - 1982 May-1983 Jan. Includes Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request, April; investigation report, Dec.; request for information by Rep. Markey, Jan. (Box 243., Folder 1-10)
      - 1983 March-1984 Jan. Ottinger/Markey Committee hearings, June 20 (Box 244., Folder 1-3)
    - Nuclear Metals, Inc. (alleged employee radiation exposure), 1983 Sept. (Folder 4)
    - Pharmaco Nuclear Inc. (alleged falsification of records), 1983 March-May (Folder 5)
    - Ray Miller, Inc. (alleged fraudulent machine parts), 1983 Jan.-Aug. (Folder 6-10)
    - Reuter-Stokes, Inc. (alleged falsification of records), 1982 May (Folder 11)
    - Rockbestos, Inc. (alleged falsification of records), 1982 May-July (Folder 12)
    - Shelwell Service, Inc. (alleged employee contamination), 1983 Sept. (Folder 13)
    - Stepan Chemical Co. (alleged radioactive thorium burial), 1980 Nov.-1982 Nov. (Box 245., Folder 1-3)
    - Transamerica-Delaval Inc. (TDI) (alleged generator problems)
      - 1983 Aug.-1984 Feb. Includes lengthy informational memoranda, 1983 Nov. and 1984 Jan.; meeting report, 1984 Feb. (Folder 4-12)
      - 1984 Feb.-1984 March. Includes meeting transcripts, the TDI Owners Group "Program Plan", and a "Component Tracking System" program applied initially to the Shoreham plant (SEE ALSO: Reactors/Shoreham), but designed for all nuclear power plants which use TDI generators; also includes an inspection report, 1979 March (Box 246., Folder 1-8)
      - 1984 March-April. Shoreham Component Tracking System (contd.) (Box 247., Folder 1-11)
  - Fuel cycle
    - General
      - General, 1973-1982. Primarily reports and speech transcripts. Includes a memorandum on breeder reactors, 1976; a report prepared for the NRC (Dr. Gilinsky) by the Pan Heuristics company entitled, "Proliferation and Plutonium Mines," 1978-1979; and material on the International Nuclear Fuel Cycle Evaluation (INFCE), 1980 (Box 248., Folder 1-8)
      - "S-3". Relates to efforts by the NRC to evaluate the cost-benefit impact of the fuel cycle over the projected lifetime operation of a light-water nuclear reactor. These values, presented in a table designated "S-3", were later found to be inadequate in the areas of reprocessing and waste management, leading to the re-evaluation effort documented in these materials
        - 1977 May-1978 Jan. (Box 249., Folder 1-8)
        - 1978 Jan. 31-1978 Nov. 16 (Box 250., Folder 1-9)
        - 1978 Nov. 16-1979 July 27. Final fuel cycle rule, July 27 (Box 251., Folder 1-11)
        - 1979 July 27 Final rule (contd.) (Box 252., Folder 1)
        - 1982 April (Folder 2)
        - 1983 Jan.-July (Folder 3)
    - Enrichment. Reports and information on the laser enrichment procedures, 1979 and 1983 (Folder 4-5)
    - Mining and milling
      - 1975 March-Sept. (Folder 6)
      - 1976 March (Folder 7)
      - 1978 April-June. Dingell Committee hearings, June 19-20 (Folder 8-9)
      - 1979 Jan.-1981 Sept. Material relating to the mill tailings dam failure in Church Rock, New Mexico, Udall Committee hearings, 1979 Oct. 22; petition by Kerr-McGee, Inc. for review of NRC uranium mill licensing regulations, 1981 Sept. (Box 253., Folder 1-13)
      - 1982 March-1983 April. Includes hearings by the H.R., Armed Services Committee, Procurement and Military Strategy Subcommittee (Samuel S. Stratton, Chairman), 1982 Aug. 16-18 (Box 254., Folder 1-12)
      - 1983 April-Dec. EPA report, April; Kerr-McGee case (Box 255., Folder 1-5)
    - Waste management
      - General. Relates predominantly to the development of a consistent federal waste management policy, with emphasis on the need for permanent high-level waste storage facilities
        - Undated (Folder 6)
        - 1976 (Folder 7)
        - 1977 Feb.-July. Relates primarily to spent fuel storage; includes an American Physical Society report (Folder 8-9)
        - 1977 Aug.-1978 May. Includes comparative material on waste management in other countries, March-April; DOE report, Feb. (Box 256., Folder 1-11)
        - 1978 June-Aug. Includes Glenn/Percy Committee hearings, July 25-27; materials on the Interagency Group on Nuclear Waste Management, July (Box 257., Folder 1-10)
        - 1978 Sept.-1979 Jan. Includes a DOE draft Environmental Impact Statement report, Sept.; and an Interagency Review Group on Nuclear Waste Management report, "Subgroup Report on Alternative Technical Strategies for the Isolation of Nuclear Waste," Oct. (Box 258., Folder 1-10)
        - 1979 Jan.-March. Udall Committee hearing, Jan. 25 (Box 259., Folder 1-10)
        - 1979 March-May 9. Includes materials on spent fuel management; staff report, March 22; hearings of the Glenn/Percy Committee, March 13-14, the Dingell Committee, Feb. 28, and the House Foreign Affairs Committee, May 3 (Box 260., Folder 1-10)